Logan Thomas

Senior Associate Data Scientist I Protection Engineering Consultants Austin, TX



About me

I'm a highly motivated and naturally curious individual with 6 years of experience using data science & machine learning techniques.

I exhibit an analytical and detailoriented nature, while placing strong value on building relationships.

Skills



Contact



≥ logan.thomas005@gmail.com

(321) 961-9107

in logan-thomas

loganthomas

Experience

Developer

Company A since January 2016 Security Clearance as of Sept 2020.

Frontend Developer

Company B January 2015 - December 2015 Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Trainee

Company C March 2014 - December 2014 Making coffee and baking cookies.

Education

Master of Arts
March 2012 - December 2013
Major in Hacking and Computer Penetration, University A, New York, USA.
Bachelor of Science
March 2009 - December 2011
Major in Engineering, University B, Los Angeles, USA.

<> Contributions

O pyjanitor	G deap	p int
Projects		
turkey-bowl	repo-scrape	python-practice